Hey, Tommy, this isn't the way to Crenshaw.
嘿 汤米 回家不该走这条路啊
There's an accident on the 10. We're taking the surface streets. - Uh-huh.
10号公路上有车祸 只好走地面道路了。 - 哦
Why are we, uh?
我们怎么...
Oh, my God.
哦 老天
He's kept tabs on her. Just in case you decided to...
他一直在暗中照看她 等你哪天想…
This was your idea, Tom? - No  -It was my idea.
这是你的主意嘛 汤姆？- 不是  - 这是我的主意
I talked him into it. - Yeah, talked him into it.  - Hey. Wait a minute, Edward.
是我说服了他  - 是啊！ 是你说服了他。 - 嘿，等一下，Edward.
Edward. What are you so afraid of?
爱德华 你干嘛那么害怕？
Just because I told you my story does not invite you to be a part of it.
我只想告诉你一个故事 又没叫你在里面瞎掺和
Oh. Like the lady in the bar?
哦 就像酒吧里的那姑娘？
- That's different.
- 那是两码事
Tell me how is it different.
怎么个两码事？
Because it is!
- 就是两码事
How is it different?
有什么区别？
You have no fucking idea who I am!
我是个什么人 你根本没概念
I built a billion-dollar business up from nothing!
我从白手起家到今天的亿万身价
Presidents have asked my advice.
连总统都要征询我的看法
I have dined with royalty and I'm supposed to make out like, what...
我和王室成员共进过晚餐， 难到还要让我理解像什么...
this trip was supposed to mean something to me?
这趟旅行对我应该有些什么意义呀？
Like it was gonna change me?
就好像，它能改变我的人生似的...
How did you see it playing out, Carter? I knock on the door, she answers. She's surprised and angry...
你认为事情该怎么发展 卡特？我敲门 然后她开门…她先是很惊讶 然后开始发火…
but I tell her how much I love her and miss her.
但我还要说 我有多么爱她多么想她
And, "Oh. By the way, I'm gonna be dead soon... so I'm reaching out to you because I don't wanna die alone"?
哦对了 "顺便说一句 我马上要死了… 所以才来找你 我不想孤零零的死"？
Everyone is afraid to die alone.
凡人都害怕孤零零的死去
I'm not everyone!
我不是凡人
This was supposed to be fun.
这次旅行本来应该很有趣
That's all it ever was.
曾经是的 但现在全完了